Guide to the Delmer Daves Papers, 1930-1965
Department of Special Collections
- Task Force, Part 1 (Warner Brothers), 1945
  - Young Aviators characterizations by Lt. Jensen. Carbon typescript., 6/15/45; 5 pages (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Notes on a Fictitious But Typical Career of a Young Pilot Who is Reporting to Aircraft Battle Force in 1922 Having Just Graduated from Pensacola. Carbon typescript., 2/23/45; 5 pages (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Notes: Rough Outline-Battle Sequence by Capt. Mort Seligman, USN(R). Carbon typescript., 5/24/45; 14 pages (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography[?] Carbon typescript., N.D.; 1 page (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Copies of Memorandums on Task Force from Mort Seligman to Ranald MacDougall. All Carbon typescript. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - re: folding wings of aircraft on carriers., 5/2/45; 1 page
    - re: Air races., 4/3/45; 1 page
    - re: Possible talk by squadron commander to new pilots when they report for duty., 3/7/45; 1 page 2 copies - one Ribbon Typescript
    - re: Naval appropriations., 2/26/45; 2 pages 2 copies - one Ribbon Typescript
    - re: Navy pilots moonlighting as test pilots., 3/16/45; 1 page 2 copies - one Ribbon Typescript
    - re: Admirals wife., 3/12/45; 1 page
    - re: Notes on `Washington Conference on the Limitations of Armaments' held Nov. 1921-Feb. 1922., N.D.; 5 pages 2 copies - one Ribbon Typescript
    - re: Application of Washington Conference to own story., 4/10/45; 2 pages
    - re: Phases of carrier picture., 2/23/45
  - Naval Aviationsand Its Problems, Etc. From 1922. Carbon typescript., 2/22/45; 18 pages (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Temporary script-part 1. Mimeo-65 pages Front cover: `Delmer Daves' in pencil holograph top of page., 6/28/45 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Screenplay by Ranald MacDougall. Carbon typescript. 189 pages Front cover: `Wald' hand-lettered in ink top of page., 8/27/45 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Screenplay by Ranald MacDougall, pages 1-13 and cast of characters. Carbon typescript with pencil holograph notes., 5/31/45; ca. 15 pages (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay by Ranald MacDougall from material by Capt. Mort Seligman, USN(R). Incomplete. ca. 38 pages Front cover: `Delmer Daves' in ink holograph [by Daves] top of page., 7/2/45 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Temporary script by Ranald MacDougall. Carbon typescript with scattered red and blue pencil additions. 65 pages Front cover: `Delmer Daves' hand-lettered in pencil top of page., 5/4/45 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Revised synopsis of opening sequences. Carbon typescript., 5/3/45; 8 pages (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Notes for the 2nd draft of Task Force. Carbon typescript., N.D.; 2 pages (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Compiled notes: (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - a.) Carrier Story Progress-Possibble Sequences. Ribbon typescript., 1 page
      Part A
    - b.) Aircraft Carrier Story-index. Ribbon typescript with ink holograph notations., 1 page
    - c.) Notes on Task Force with dates of 4/20, 5/3, and 5/25/45. Ribbon typescript., ca. 24 pages
    - d.) Lt. Jonathan Scott, Personal Story. Ribbon typescript., 8 pages
    - e.) Scene breakdown and synopsis. Ribbon typescript with scattered pencil and ink holograph notations., ca. 47 pages (Box 21, Folder 19)
      Part B
    - f.) My Favorite War Story by Moscrip Miller. Ribbon typescript., 5/22/45; 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 20)
      Pt. C
    - g.) Signed memo: Oliver Jensen to Jerry Wald re: outline of fictitious final battle for Task Force. Ribbon typescript., 1 page
    - h.) Preliminaries-at anchor, Autumn, 1945 by Lt. Jensen. Ribbon typescript., 5/15/45; ca. 41 pages (Box 21, Folder 21)
      Pt. D
    - i.) Flagship bridge-Geography. Ribbon typescript., 3 pages (Box 21, Folder 22)
      E
    - j.) Rough Outline of Battle Sequences by Mort Seligman. C Carbon typescript., 5/24/45; 12 pages
    - K*N: re: M.A. Mitscher, Navy Officer.
      - k.) Baltimore Sun- article by E.T. Baker. Ribbon typescript., 7/16/44; 4 pages
        all part of one article
      - l.) Philadelphia Record- article by Lief Erickson. Ribbon typescript., 7/16/44; 2 pages
      - m.) Navy Department-Biographical Section. Ribbon typescript., 1/29/42; 2 pages
      - n.) Navy Department Press Release. Ribbon typescript., 11/21/44; 1 page
    - o.) Jumping Joe Clifton. Ribbon typescript., 3 pages
    - p.), Carrier Chaplain by Lt. Jensen. Carbon typescript., 5/25/45; 11 pages
    - q.) Chief Petty Officer-Flight Deck by Lt. Jensen. Carbon typescript., 5/25/45; 4 pages
    - r.) Doctor by Lt. Jensen. Carbon typescript., 5/25/45; 3 pages
    - s.) Newspaper clipping: Mates Rescue Flyers Downwed Amid Jap Ships in Enemy Sea by Grant McDonald., 5/18/?
  - Task Force (from Washington D.C. to end) - outline of sequences. Carbon typescript., 7/30/45; 4 pages (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Aircraft Carrier story notes by Ranald MacDougall with Capt. Seligman. Research notes by James Smith re: exact chronology of a fictitious Navy admiral. Carbon typescript., N.D.; 43 pages (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Comments by J.S. Thack re: Task Force. Ribbon typescript., 9/28/45; 19 pages (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Memo: Mort Saligman to Ranald MacDougall re: Task Force. Carbon typescript., 3/12/45; 1 page (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Scene breakdown and synopsis. Carbon typescript. 40 pages 1st Page: `Daves' hand-lettered in red pencil top of page., N.D. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Typed letter signed: Olle Comstedt to Delmer Daves re: obtaining information about mining., 10/2/48 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Notes on a Fictitious But Typical Career of a Young Pilot Who is Reporting to Aircraft Battle Force in 1922 Having Just Graduated from Pensacola. by Mort Seligman. Ribbon typescript., 2/23/45; 3 page (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Aircraft Carrier- story notes (parts 1,2,3). Mimeo- with occasional pencil and ink holograph changes and notations. 120 pages Front cover: `Task Force!' hand-lettered in pencil above title. `Wald' in ink holograph at top of page., 4/4/45 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Forward and story outline. Mimeo-with occasional pencil and ink holograph notations and changes. 21 pages Included with above: additions to story outline. Ribbon typescript. 3 pages, 6/11/45 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Principal Personel Involved In Carrier Story. Carbon typescript., 5/10/45; 4 pages (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Locations and outline of scemes. Carbon typescript., N.D.; ca. 28 pages (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Navy film footage reviewed and selected by Delmer Daves. Carbon typescript with `Daves' in pencil and ink at top of some pages., 3-7/45; ca. 231 pages (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Memo to Ranald Mac Douglas Subject: Carrier Story, 3/9/45 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Naval Aviation Notes, 4/3/45 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- The Red House (Lesser-United Artists); 1948 A Kiss In The Dark (Warner Brothers)., 1946
  - Pete's Story (The Red House) story notes by Delmer Daves. Ribbon typescript. 15 pages 1st page: `The Red House-D.D.' hand-lettered in ink at top of page., N.D. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - The Red House screenplay by Delmer Daves. Mimeo- with occasional pencil scene sketches in margins, and pencil holograph c changes. Included in screenplay: changes on blue paper with dates of 5/21, 5/22, and 5/24/46-12 pages; changes in carbon typescript 4 pages. Total screenplay:, 4/14/46; ca. 135 pages (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - A Kiss in the Dark shooting script by Delmer Daves; original screenplay by Harvey Kurnity from the story Cleopatra Aims by Everett Freeman-1948. Mimeo- with scattred pencil scene sketches in margins and on verso of pages 136 and 139, and pencil holograph changes. Included in script: changes on pink paper with dates of 3/17, 3/25, 4/1, and 4/5/48; ca. 34 pages. Total screenplay:, N.D.; ca. 139 pages (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Dark Passage (Warner Brothers), 1946-47
  - Typed letter signed: Jerry Wald to Delmer Daves re: shots needed. On Warner Brothers stationary with some pencil holograph additions., 11/18/46; 2 pages (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Typed letter signed: Jerry Wald to Delmer Daves re: report on quality of completed shots. On Warner Brothers stationary., 11/19/46; 2 pages
  - Typed letter signed: Jerry Wald to Delmer Daves re: report on quality of completed shots. On Warner Brothers stationary., 11/21/46; 2 pages
  - San Francisco location, scene descriptions-Dick Mayberry. Ribbon typescript., 9/27/46; 10 pages (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Inter-office communication: Ken Cox to W.L. Guthrie re: San Francisco scene locations. Carbon typescript., 9/28/46; 3 pages (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Set descriptions by Carl J. Weyl, Art Director. Carbon typescript., 9/17/46; 2 pages (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco location, scene descriptions-Dick Mayberry. Carbon typescript., 9/27/46; 10 pages (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Western Unoin Telegram: Jack [Warner] to Delmar Daves., 9/30/[46] (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Brown copies (similar to blueprints) of sketches, outlined in red and orange crayon, of floor pland for sets in Dark Passage., N.D.; 8 pages (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Observations of the Camera Acting as a Person-Dark Passage. Ribbon typescript. 4 pages 1st page: `Appendix to Technical Notes' hand-lettered in pencil top of page., N.D. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Notes on experimental camera work. Carbon typescript., N.D.; 1 page (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Inter-office comunication: Delmer Daves to all departments re: technical notes., 10/22/46; Mimeo- 28 pages (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Brown copies (similar to blueprints) of sketches, outlined in red and orange crayon, of floor plans for scene layouts., N.D. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - a.) 8½×11", 9 pages
    - b.) 13×15½", 1 page
    - c.) 8½×14", 4 pages
  - Typed letter (copy): Joseph I. Breen to J.L. Warner re: censoring Dark Passage. Ribbon typescript., 6/5/46; 3 pages (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Typed letter (copy): Joseph I. Breen to J.L. Warner re: censoring Dark Passage. Ribbon tyupescript., 10/17/46; 2 pages
  - Inter-office communication: Phil Friedman to arner, Trilling, Wald, Wright, Kumin, Levinson, Westmore, Hansen, Mayberry. Initialed by Phil Friedman at bottom of page. Carbon typescript., 10/18/46; 1 page (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Typed letter signed: Clinton T. Duffy (Warden, San Quentin Prison) to Kenneth Cox.re: permisson to take a long shot motion picture of prison. Carbon typescript., 9/24/46; 1 page (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous pages of dialogue. Ribbon typescript., N.D.; 3 pages (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Cutting notes from David Weisbart from Delmer Daves. Carbon tyupescript., N.D.; 10 pages (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - a.) Cast and credits., N.D.; Mimeo- 1 page (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - b.), Synopsis of story., Mimeo- 1 page
  - c.) Production notes., Mimeo- 4 pages
  - Index to scene breakdown., 10/18/46; Mimeo- ca. 85 pages (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay by Delmer Daves from the novel by David Goodis. Carbon typescript., 5/46; 131 pages (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Screenplay by Delmer Daves. Mimeo- with blue page changes dated 9/9/46.ca. 131 pages Ribbon typescript note by Delmer Daves on title page re: Jack Warners reluctance to use new camera technique (in which the camera was to be Bogart for the first part of the film); Bob Montgomery's use of this technique (borrowed from Daves) in his film Lady of the Lake, for which Montgomery got credit for originating a new camera technique; Daves' use-first ever- of the hand-held AERO-FLEX camera., 5/24/46 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - a.) Story analyzed by Dorthea Cartwright Doe., 11/25/45; Mimeo- 2 pages (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - b.) Story analyzed by Lenyth Soares., 11/14/45; Mimeo- 15 pages
  - Galley proofs of Dark Passage by David Goodis., 12/31/45; ca. 75 pages (Box 23, Folder 17)
- To The Victor (Warner Brothers), 1947
  Note: 1-26 are bound together
  - Delmer Daves- biographical s sketches in French., N.D.; Mimeo- 1 page (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Inter-office communication: Alex Evelove to Delmer Daves. Ribbon typescript., 6/20/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter: Jerry Wald to Frank McCarthy. Carbon typescript., 7/5/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter: Jerry Wald to Rene Claire. Carbon typescript., 7/5/47; 1 page
  - Addresses: Andre Hakim and Frank McCarthy. Ribbon typescript., N.D.; 1 page
  - Additional possible shots to be made by Delmer Daves in Paris. Carbon typescript., 6/25/47; 1 page
  - Envelope (8¼×8) to Mr. and Mrs. Delmer Daves, Appt. 320/21 Hotel George V, Paris., N.D.
  - Shipping report for films, signed by Eaelene Hicks. Carbon typescript., 6/30/47; 1 page
  - Shipping report for films, signed by Earlene Hicks. Carbon typescript., 7/1/47; 1 page
  - Inter-office communication: William T. Orr to Dalmar Daves [sic] re: Miss Lisber. Ribbon typescript, on octavo, initialed by Orr. 1 page Included with above: 2 photographs (4×6") of Miss Lisber., 7/8/47
  - Western Union Telegram: Jack Warner to Mr. and Mrs. Delmar Daves [sic]., 7/11/47
  - Western Union Telegram: Jerry Wald to Mr. and Mrs Delmer Daves., 7/11/47
  - Western Union Telegram: Milt Grossman to Delmer Daves., 7/11/47
  - Western Union Telegram: Milt Grossman to Delmer Daves., 7/11/47
  - Western Union Telegram: Milt Grossman to Delmar Daves [sic]., 7/11/47
  - Typed letter signed: Jerry Wald to Delmer Daves re: addresses of contacts in Paris. On Warner Brothers stationary., 7/8/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter signed: Oliver Jensen to Jerry Wald re: asking to have Delmer Daves call on way through New York., 7/2/47
  - Inter-office communication: Sophie Rosenstein to Delmar Daves sic. re: French talent. Ribbon typescript., 7/8/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter signed: Jerry Wald to Delmer Daves. Ribbon typescript on Warner Brothers stationary. 1 page Included on page: Ink holograph notation probably by Wald Best to the bunch. On verso: Ink holograph note by `Lil', reporting on `Michael and Debbie' Daves' children., 7/12/47
  - Typed letter signed (in French): Mme. L. Rouiez, Secretaire-Andre Bernheim, to Delmer Daves re: photograph of Marcel Dailio. 1 page Included with above: envelope addressed to `Mr. Delmer Daves'., 7/15/47
  - Autographed letter signed: (in French): Christian Fontugue [to Delmer Daves] re: bringing a picture (tableau)., 7/19/47
  - Trip schedule: Party of 7 people leaving for Chicago and Los Angeles. Ribbon typescript. 1 page On verso: Ink holograph note, Del! Welcome back to Paree! Joe H., N.D.
  - Inter-office communication: Delmer Daves to Jack Warner re: budget and time schedule of Tom The Victor. Carbon typescript., 10/24/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter signed: Joseph H. Westreich to Delmer Daves re: shipping painting out of France to be used in To The Victor. On Warner Brothers (Paris) stationary., 10/31/47; 1 page
  - Typed letter: H. Descombes to J. Westreich re: exportation of a painting for Mr. Delmer Daves., N.D.; 1 page
  - Typed letter signed: Joseph H. Westreich to Delmer Daves re: release of To The Victor., 11/26/47
  - Breakdown of scenes with `studio needs'. Blueprint. ca. 37 pages (3 copies of above), N.D.
  - Copy A (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Copy B (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Copy C (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Pre-planning Studio Use of Process Plates- photographs (5×8") of locations, with their corresponding scene sketch. On quarto., N.D.; ca. 29 pages (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Paris exteriors- locations and descriptions of needed shots. Ribbon typescript., 7/12/47; 29 pages (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Wardrobe chart., 6/11/47; Mimeo- 15 pages (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Paris shooting script, original screenplay by Richard Brooks. Mimeo- with occasional pencil scene sketches in the margins and on verso (most approx. 1½×2"), and pencil holograph additions and deletions., N.D.; 141 pages (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 2nd revised temporary script., 7/1/47; Mimeo- 141 pages (Box 24, Folder 5)
- The 20th Anniversary Academy Awards written and directed by Delmer Daves, 1948
  - Floor plan of the Al Malaikah Temple in Los Angeles, Calif. (13½×17") Main floor and balcony., N.D.; 2 pages (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Director's Credit Bulletin 1946-47 Screen Director's Guild, Inc., N.D.; 15 pages (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Program: Series of Screenings of the Nominations for the 20th Annual Awards, Feb. 21-March 12, 1948., N.D. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Program: 19th Annual Academy Awards., 3/13/47; 8 pages (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Revised tentative program for 19th Annual Academy Awards at Shrine Auditorium from William Cannon., 3/13/47; Mimeo- 30 pages (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Agenda: Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences Board of Governors meeting., 1/13/48; Mimeo- 1 page (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Agenda: Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences Board of Governors meeting., 2/19/48; Mimeo- 1 page
  - Notes by Delmer Daves on Board of Governors meeting. Ribbon typescript., 1/13/48; 1 page
  - The 20th Anniversary Academy Awards suggested program by Delmer Daves., 1/12/48; Mimeo- 22 pages (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The 20th Anniversary Academy Awards revised program by Delmer Daves. Mimeo- 18 pages (3 copies of above), 2/20/48
  - Copy A (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - B (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - C (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - The 20th Anniversary Academy Awards revised by Delmer Daves., 3/12/48; Mimeo- 19 pages (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - The 20th Anniversary Academy Awards suggested program by Delmer Daves. Carbon typescript with occasional ink holograph notations., N.D.; 22 pages (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 20th Awards budget summary. Mimeo- 6 pages 1st page: `Delmer Daves' in ink holograph top of page., 1/13/48 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Draft: Academy of Motion Picture Picture Arts and Sciences procedure for counting ballots under preferential system., N.D.; Mimeo- 2 pages (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Booklet: Report of the President to the Members of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences., 5/25/48; 12 pages (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Booklet: 20th Annual Academy Awards Rules for the Conduct of the Balloting., N.D.; 16 pages (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Booklet: By-laws of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences., 1/1/48; 15 pages (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Booklet: 20th Annual Academy Awards for Achievements During 1947-Reminder List of Elgible Released Durung the Year. 24 pages (2 copies), N.D. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Typed letter signed: Ralph Staub to Delmer Daves re: `Screen Snapshots!., 1/15/48; 1 page (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences 1947 obituary list, secured from Variety magazine. Ribbon typescript., 1/9/48; 3 pages (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Typed letter signed: Memorandum, Margaret Herrick to Delmer Daves re: 20th Academy Awards., 12/9/48; 1 page (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Task Force, Part 3 (Warner Brothers), 1948
  - Final (shooting) script. Mimeo- with scattered pencil and ink holograph additions and deletions and some ink scene sketches in margins. Holograph notes on title page, and `ship' dialogue in pencil, taped over cast of characters page. 131 pages Included with above: Notes on `ship' dialogue in pencil (5½×8" paper). 2 pages b.) Receipt from Union Oil Co.. for charged services, signed by Mrs. Delmer Daves., 10/22/48 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Shooting schedule., 10/25/48; Mimeo- 22 pages (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Index to breakdown, set list, and breakdown of sequences., 8/31/45; Mimeo- 163 pages (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of pencil diagrams of sets., 9/11/45; 12 pages (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of airccaft carrier `Hornet'., 9/11/45; ca. 53 prints (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Brown copies (similar to blueprints) of Int. CIC and Air Plot (20×30)-, N.D.; 2 copies (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Personnel and duty list., N.D.; Mimeo- 1 page (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of pencil and ink drawings of scenes., N.D.; ca. 135 sketches. (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
- Task Force Part IV (WB), 1949
  - Notes on temporary script by Mort Seligman as revised by Delmer Daves. Carbon typescript., 7/10/45; 79 pgs. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Personnel list of people and jobs in film, Task Force. Mimeographed copy., 10/19/49; 5 pgs. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Task Force personnel list for on board ship by Joe Barry with room and telephone numbers. Mimeographed copy., 10/25/48; 4 pgs. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Inter-office communication: T. C. Wright to all members of the Task Force Company re: regulations on ship. Mimeographed copy., 10/18/49; 2 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - TLC from Co. V. Peterson, Commanding Officer to Commander, Fleet Air West West Coast re: tentative employment schedule, 10/23 to 11/48., N.D.; 2 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - History of the Preparation and Making of the Film, Task Force (1945-1949). T., N.D.; 1 pg. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Memo from U. S. S. Antietam to WB motion picture team re: ship regulations. M. legal size., N.D.; 1 pg. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Schedule for shooting scenes on board. T with FPpNAD and P sketches., N.D.; 8vo. 19 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Cast and crew room and telephone number assignments on board ship. T with 8vo cardboard backing., N.D.; 1 pg. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Wine list of commissioned officers mess, Naval AirkStation, Alameda, Calif., with signatures-Daves, Walter Brennan, J. V. Peterson, Gary Cooper, W. R. McClintock, G. J. Hedding. Larger than 16mo., N.D. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - TL copies (4), Joseph I. Breen to J. L. Warner re: censorship of parts of Task Force. T copy with 3 C., 10/26/48; 4 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Comments by J. S. Thach on MacDougall script. C with PNAD on pg. 2 and FpNAD elsewhere by DD., 9/28/45; 18 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Combined critique on Task Force with OpNAD. C., 9/17/45; 15 pgs.
  - General notes on Task Force by DD. C., 9/19/45; 2 pgs.
  - Suggested revisions on Task Force by Lt. David Hopkins. C., 9/12/45; 7 pgs.
  - Notes on Task Force by Lt. Cmdr. Eggert., 9/21/45
  - Task Force - final script by DD and ronald MacDougall with OpNAD. M., 10/22/48; 131 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - For Spacious Skies- SP by Ronald MacDougall and DD with PN on cover explaining his rewriting the script in in 1948, and PN on script. C., 10/27/45; 161 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Task Force - SP by DD. C., 10/9/45; 161 pgs.
  - Insert - notes on In Which We Serve by DD. C., 6/1/48; 10 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Memo to Jerry Wald re: outline to fictitious battle for Task Force with suggestions by LT. Jensen. Carbon., 5/15/45; 42 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Task Force 2 - 2nd Rev. Temp. Script Part IV to end with DD Signature on cover and OpNAD. M., 10/20/48; 19 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Music Publisher's Holding Corp. list of songs popular, 1919 - 1948 with PN and phone numbers of John Gilbraith and Frank Ryan. T., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Make-up progression charts for Task Force., 10/9/48; 3pp. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Task Force 2 - Rev. Temp. Script Part I with SpNAD. M., 10/5/48; 115 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Blank sheet with mimeo heading: Task Force Cast of Characters., 10/14/48; 1 pg. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - IOC re: Carl Milliken to Kissel re: sinking of Langley by Japanese planes; excerpt from Battle Report: Pearl Harbor to Coral Sea by King and Kelly, 2/27/42., 10/13/48
  - IOC Stacey to Wright, Friedman, Daves, 10/18/48
  - Kissel and Tinsmen re: cast list, wardrobe and make-up. C.
  - Task Force - Rev. SP by DD with OpN by DD. C., 10/9/45; 123 pg. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Task Force 2 - 2nd Rev. Temp. Part I with DD signature. [UNK], 10/7/48; 81 pg. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Task Force - final SP with DD signature on cover. M., 10/22/48; 131 pgs. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Memo - Lt. Oliver Jensen to JW re: notes on air craft carrier story. C., 5/4/45; 5 pgs. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - From Lt. Oliver Jensen re: information on Kamikaze pilots and other aspects of Japanese force. C., 5/3/45; 7pgs. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Task Force by DD re: production, script and background information., 5/18/48; 3 pgs. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - List of Navy bases and ships (with years) and commanding officers., ND (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - pN on Bureau of Yards and Dock memo sheet 8vo with 1 pg. of information on verso re: sets, production, sequences., ND (Box 27, Folder 5)